module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is Jerrys real name in Parks and Rec?',
    a: 'Garry',
    b: 'Terry',
    c: 'Larry',
    d: 'Jerry',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are call letters of Frasiers radio station?',
    a: 'KCAL',
    b: 'CALK',
    c: 'KACL',
    d: 'KCAL',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Captain Holts dog?',
    a: 'Cheddar',
    b: 'Bacon',
    c: 'Spot',
    d: 'Sgt. Cuddlebutt',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What color is the couch in Central Perk?',
    a: 'Red',
    b: 'Orange',
    c: 'Grey',
    d: 'Black',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is NOT a George Costanza alias?',
    a: 'Koko the Monkey',
    b: 'Art Vanderlay',
    c: 'Colin O Brien',
    d: 'H E Pennypacker',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the banana stand mascot created by GOB?',
    a: 'Bananahands',
    b: 'Bananarama',
    c: 'Mr Yellow',
    d: 'Bananagrabber',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which character went to high school with Michael Scott?',
    a: 'Phyllis',
    b: 'Todd Packer',
    c: 'Dwight',
    d: 'Kevin',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was Ned Flanders wifes name?',
    a: 'Ruth',
    b: 'Edna',
    c: 'Maude',
    d: 'Margaret',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Whose house do The Golden Girls live in?',
    a: 'Blanche',
    b: 'Sophia',
    c: 'Rose',
    d: 'Dorothy',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the name of the restuarant above Cheers?',
    a: 'Bull & Finch',
    b: 'Melvilles',
    c: 'The Hungry Heifer',
    d: 'Little Wallys',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];